Lines of text we never check.
Scroll and tap without regret.
Contract ink that's dry and cold.
Sold our souls or so we're told.
Promises they'll never keep.
Barely with you before we sleep.
Paper walls around our heads.
Hoping nothing will be said.
Sign your name, just press agree.
Never read a word they write.
We don't ding so easily.
Take your lever and swipe.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Pages long in legalese Promises beneath the fees Scroll right to the end, we're blind Stuck but say we're doing fine Clicking faster than we pace Tracking digital routines
Swept away by all the screams.
Sign your name, just press agree.
Never read a word they write.
Flavco tastes so dizzily.
Take you have the rest, why?